Guide to the Stanford University, El Centro Chicano, Records SC0650
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional materials, Accession ARCH-2005-210
  - Unsorted
    - Human Resource Group 1986 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Inter-University Program For Latino Research 1988 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Chicano Fellows Reading Room- Biblio 1980 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - La Raza Staff 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Human Resources Committee 1982 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Raza Staff Finances 1982 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Latin American Studies (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Stanford Chicano Organizations Publications 1980-1985 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Latino Freshmen 1986 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Media on Hispanic Americans, Meyer Library 1980-1987 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Mexican American Collections 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Opportunities Retreat (Fernando de Necochea) (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Psycho-Structural Issues Affecting Latino Students at Stanford 1989 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - La Raza Staff Association 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - 1987-1988 Raza Staff Roster (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Raza Staff Nominations 1989 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - School of Engineering HELP Sessions 1986-1987 Report (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Graduate Development Program 1987 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Ho Fund Guidelines (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Inst. Responses to Racism & Prejudice, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Math HELP Sessions 1987 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Minority Outreach (1988-1989) (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Minority Outreach Program 1988 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Minority Student Recruitment PGM. 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Race/Culture Newspaper Clippings 1987 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Raza Staff, Human Resource Committee 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Res Ed/Theme Houses/Guidelines 1986 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Stanford Summer Introduction to Research Program 1989 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Aids/Latinos 1987 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Ambassador Program 1986 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - American Indian Summer Institute PGM. 1989 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Asian Americans at Stanford, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Asian American Dean, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Black Community Services Center, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Black Community Service Center Budget Proposal 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Bunzel Report on Theme Houses, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Chicano/Latino Community Service Network, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Committee on Quality of Minority Life, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - The Compelling Community Cultural Center, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Ethnic Theme Center Staff (85-86) (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Faculty/Staff Awards 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Galarza Commemorative Lecture '86 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - "Spirit of Hoover"/ Casa Zapata 1986 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - U.C.M.I. 1988 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - University Committee on Minority Issues (UCMI)-1988 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Sanctuary/Central America 1985 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Stanford Ctr for Chicano Research, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Tresidder Staff: Working With Chicano/Hispanic Students & Staff. 1988 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Undergrad Chicano Enrollment Figures, 1981-1985 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Western Culture, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Workshop on Hispanic Advising Needs, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Committee to Review the Office of Chicano Affairs, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - CGSA Seminar. 1985 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - "Ethnicity & Public Service" 1985 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Minority Staff Concerns, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - Accelerated Learning & Productivity Syst. (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - AD HOC Committee on Academic Performance 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - "Adopt-A-Fellow", 1989 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - "Adopt-A-School", 1987 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Advising Group 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Alcohol Policy (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - ASSU Council of Presidents, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - Stanford University Budget Reductions, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - Career Planning & Placement Center, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Catering Services (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - Center For Teaching & Learning Advisory Committee 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - Stanford Community Fund Board 1985 (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - Community Service Ctr. Assessment Proj. 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 99)
    - Concession Sales-Guidelines 1986 (Box 18, Folder 100)
    - Conference Information 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 101)
    - Dean's Award for Service 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 102)
    - Dean's Award for Service 1985 (Box 18, Folder 103)
    - Dean's Group 1986 (Box 18, Folder 104)
    - Disability Resource Center, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 105)
    - Stanford Ethical Issues, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 106)
    - Freshman Advising, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 107)
    - Freshman Advisor Appointment 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 108)
    - Freshman English Course 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 109)
    - Freshman Orientation Parents' Day Convocations, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 110)
    - Fundraising Support Groups, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 111)
    - Health And Safety, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 112)
    - Human Resources Group 1986 (Box 18, Folder 113)
    - ID Mail, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 114)
    - Koret Fund 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 115)
    - Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Community Center (1988-1989) (Box 18, Folder 116)
    - Mentor Program 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 117)
    - Operation Safe Schools 1988 (Box 18, Folder 118)
    - Committee on Public Events. 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 119)
    - Public Service Group-CPPC 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 120)
    - RES ED Program Funding Guidelines 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 121)
    - Robinson Humanitarian Award 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 122)
    - Robinson Student Humanitarian Achievement Award 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 123)
    - Stanford In Government 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 124)
    - Student/Police Relations Panel, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 125)
    - Tax-Exempt Status (Box 18, Folder 126)
    - Tips/Class 1988 (Box 18, Folder 127)
    - Tresidder Programs, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 128)
    - Tutoring, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 129)
    - Undergraduate Data 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 130)
    - University Lecture Fund 1987 (Box 18, Folder 131)
    - United Stanford Workers (Box 18, Folder 132)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network 1985 (Box 18, Folder 133)
    - Volunteer Coordinator Selection Public Service Center 1986 (Box 18, Folder 134)